It's been a long time.
お久しぶりです
So cute.
すっごいかわいい
thank you.
ありがとうございます
It's really cute though
めちゃめちゃかわいいんだけど、
Are you in love?
恋 してる?
ERROR
恋ですか?
They say you become beautiful when you're in love.
恋してるときれいになるって言うじゃん
The nose is so chewy.
もちもちじゃん、鼻が
Is it true?
ほんとですか?
Because I'm eating a lot of rice.
ご飯たくさん食べてるから
What did you eat yesterday?
昨日何食べた?
yesterday?
昨日?
Red Tang?
赤唐?
I like it.
好きなんだ
Are you going to eat a lot of rice?
ご飯いっぱい食べるの?
ERROR
食べます、たくさん
The style is really nice to me.
その俺にはスタイルがすごいいいしね
No, not at all.
いや、全然
ERROR
なんか、やってるんだよね?
まあ、ダンスしてます
hey.
ね
Isn't it amazing?
すごいんでしょ?
Yeah.
うん
ERROR
練習してます、今ずっと
I'm practicing.
練習してるんだ
Backed by a famous artist?
有名なアーティストのバックで?
that's right.
そうです
I'm back dancing.
バックダンスをしてます
Do you want to do that exercise?
その演習をしたいってこと?
whose?
誰 の?
I can see it.
俺、目にくわ
thank you.
ありがとうございます
It feels like this.
この感じだけど
Ah, I think it's good.
あー、いいと思う
Stand out, stand out.
目立つ、目立つ
stand out?
目立つ?
Have you had an inch recently?
最近、インチしました?
No, I don't know.
いや、知ってないです
For a moment, I felt like something came to mind.
ちょっと、何か一人思い浮かんだ感じして
No, I don't know.
いや、知ってないです
real?
ほ んと?
Even though you don't know me, do you have such sex appeal?
知ってないのに、そんな色気が出るの?
Eat a lot of food and sleep a lot.
たくさんご飯食べて、たくさん寝る
Ah, like an elementary school student.
あ、小学生のような
Yeah.
うん
Move well.
元気に動いて
That's right, that's right.
そうです、そうです
Eat well.
元気に食べて
sleep?
寝る?
ERROR
大 人の女の子は、そこにたくさんエッチするっていうのがないと
It's no good.
ダ メなんだよ
Is it true?
本当ですか?
At the beginning.
最初で
Do you have sex alone?
一人エッチとかします?
I don't.
しないです
Is that so?
そうなの?
Wow, there are a lot of things like picking up girls and calling out to them, right?
すごい、ナンパとか声かけたりとか多いでしょ?
Yeah, Scout?
うん、スカウト?
scout?
スカウト?
What kind of scout?
どんなスカウト?
Would you like to join a talent agency?
芸能事務所入りませんか?
Like.
みたいな
I'm a little worried.
ちょっと悩んでます
That's right.
そうなんだ
Just do it.
やればいいじゃん
Well, I'm not confident.
えー、自信ない
Not confident?
自信ない?
It's very stylish, too.
とっても、スタイルも良くて
I'm not confident.
自信ないです
Really?
本当に?
I'll support you.
応援しますよ
Is it true?
本当ですか?
Yes, number 1.
はい、1号目
Yes, is that okay?
はい、いいですか?
This is the second issue.
こちら2号目で
I'll sign it.
サイン書きますから
Yes, is that okay?
はい、いいですか?
Let's practice a little handshake event.
ちょっと握手会の練習しておきます
Ah, then.
あ、じゃあ
I always watch it.
いつも見てます
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Just give me a handshake
ちょっと握手して
please.
ください
Did the handshake event go like this?
握 手会ってこんなにしたっけ?
Shouldn't you stand?
立つんじゃない?
Are you going to stand?
立つん?
緊張
Are you nervous?
緊張してるの?
My hands are sweaty and sticky.
手汗がベトベトね
I'm nervous.
緊張してる
It's kind of interesting.
なんか面白い
I'm sweating.
汗なってる
Is this interesting?
これが面白い?
Please smile.
笑ってくれ
It's okay to laugh.
笑っていいよ
It's okay to laugh because there are two of us.
2人いるから笑っていい
2人 いる から笑っていい
But, I don't understand the meaning of the first issue having multiple faces.
でも ね、1号目が複面する意味はわかんないけどね
Please give me a spatula later.
ちょっと後でヘラしてあげてください
Please smile.
笑ってくれ
I'm sweating a little, so maybe
ちょっと汗かいてるから、もしかしたら
...
It's embarrassing.
恥 ずかしい
Like an aunt.
おばさんみたいな
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいです
It's a little intense.
ちょっと激しいです
Because it's been a while.
久々だから
Yeah.
うん
Because it's been a while.
久々だから
It's been a long time since you last saw me in red?
久 々だから赤にしがんじゃったの?
What if I don't touch it?
触らないとどう?
Are you standing on your butt?
なんかお尻に立ってるの?
Yeah.
うん
amazing.
すごい
Just a little.
ちょっとさ
Wear naughty underwear.
エッチな下着履いて
Those are really beautiful feet.
すっごい綺麗な足だね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
So, show me your butt again.
で、お尻をもう一回見せて
She's in a really nice shape.
すっごいますっきめな体勢になってる
I like this see-through underwear.
この透けてる下着がいいね
Oh, it's a little wet.
あ、ちょっと濡れてる
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It's hot, isn't it?
暑いもんね
Is it hot?
暑いの?
Okay, stockings.
いいよね、ストッキング
I got wet.
濡れた
this.
これ
I've included a little bit of this.
これちょい含めずし
Is it decided?
お決まりの?
Oh, I got wet.
あ、濡れた
Wet feet are the best.
濡れた足最高だ
sorry.
ごめんなさい
difficult.
難しい
Wow, that's sexy.
わぁ、セクシー
amazing.
すごい
So sexy.
めちゃめちゃセクシー
I have to fall in love.
恋しなきゃね
I really like Stal.
スタルいいね、ほんとに
That's sexy, right there.
セクシーだよ、そこ
Hmm, shh.
うーん、しー
Shi.
しー